aegissofttech.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy

We at Aegis Software are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

Aegis Software has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

This policy (“Privacy Statement”) is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any personal information we obtain about you based upon your use of our website, products or services.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an e-mail address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Aegis Software’s web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the web, we may transfer that Information, within Aegis Software or to Aegis Software third party service providers, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Aegis Software strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy.

Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Aegis Software intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred or retained. The applicable privacy statement sets forth your and our rights and responsibilities with regard to your personal information.

For further information, mail us at[ info@aegissofttech.com](mailto:info@aegissofttech.com)
